Hi. You've reached Nikki.
If you cannot leave a message, you
better have something good to say!
Hey. It's me.
I'm about to go into Alice's.
If you want to stop by
after work, please do.
It'd be great to see you.
If not, I will see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
Hey!
Look at you.
Where's Nik?
She's at work, but she might
stop by later, though.
Okay.
Single girl tonight, then, hmm?
Come on. Let's get us a drink.
What are you having?
I think you've already had enough.
Oh, hush, hush.
Come on. What are you having?
Just get me a beer.
All right.
Hey, Sam.
Hey.
Riley.
Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I thought Alice said you
might not be coming.
Yeah, it was a last-minute thing.
Cool.
Can I get you a drink?
Oh, no, no.
Alice just went to
get me something.
Okay. Oh, of course.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For... assuming, um...
Hey. It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
So are you still
seeing that bartender?
I'm gonna run to the
bathroom really quick.
Sorry.
'Cause who cares?
Like, pick me up, you know?
Oh, sorry. Hold on.
Sam.
Hey.
Zain.
What's up?
Nothing.
It's been... a long time.
You been good?
Yeah.
I'm trying to.
Uh...
where's Nik?
Is that-did I say...
Sorry.
Did I say something weird?
No.
You know what?
It's fine.
Forget it.
Okay.
'Cause I'm about to go to the
bathroom, if you need a bump.
I'm good.
It'll help.
Thanks.
Really.
All right.
Well, let me know.
Do you need some help with that?
I got you a drink.
Oh, what is in that?
Vodka.
And what else?
This isn't what I asked for.
Oh, it's alcohol.
Come on. You'll love it.
Shots.
Come on.
Shots solve everything.
I can't do two shots.
Well, you're not gonna do two shots.
You're gonna do four shots.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no.
I-I can't.
Quick.
Are you trying to get me drunk?
Yes!
If Nikki shows up,
she's gonna kill me.
Oh, fuck her.
She's not gonna show up.
Alice...
Drink.
Come on.
Just do it before
you think about it.
Quick, before you think
about it, just do it.
Fine.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Oh.
Hurry before you regret
your life choices.
Might as well look
elsewhere, my friend.
She is no longer interested in
what our kind have to offer.
Yay.
Ugh.
W...
Uh-oh.
You know, Riley's on the prowl.
He can sense that the alcohol
is taking over your body.
He's gonna sit there
silently, off to the side,
until he senses that you've thrown
all your inhibitions to the wind,
and that's when he's
gonna make his move,
sweeping you off of your
feet and into his bed.
Oh, as if that would help.
Hey, Riley.
Sam says if you can eat
pussy like a lesbian,
then she'll take you for a
ride in about an hour or so.
Alice, what the fuck are you doing?
Oh, come on.
He knows I'm kidding.
Well, someone has to tell that
kid he doesn't have a chance.
And you had to tell
half the party, as well.
I don't know half these
people, anyways.
Hi.
You've reached Nikki.
If you cannot leave a message,
you better have
something good to say!
Beep!
Hey.
It's...
it's almost 2:00.
I guess you're not coming.
I probably shouldn't
be calling you, but...
I can't help it.
I'm thinking of you...
a lot.
And...
I'm not sure how much
longer I'm gonna stay.
So...
I guess I'll see you
in the morning.
Okay.
I love you.
Shit!
Look what you made me do.
I'm so sorry.
I'll help you clean that up.
Here's your drink.
Did I have a drink?
I don't even remember
what I was doing.
I'm pretty sure
I saw you holding it.
Are you spying on me?
I thought you looked...
interesting.
Interesting.
Haven't heard that one before.
I think I saw you earlier.
You know Alice?
I came here with a friend,
B.J.
How does your friend know Alice?
I'm not sure.
Is your friend a girlfriend and
you're just not saying it?
No, it's not.
How about you?
Are you here with anyone?
No.
I'm not.
Hmm.
Well, are you seeing anyone?
Yeah. I am.
He's a lucky guy.
Girl.
How long has that been going on?
Me being a lesbian or me and her?
Both.
Same time.
Are you intimidated?
A little.
Why isn't she here
with you tonight?
We should stop.
I'm serious.
Please?
Please.
Oh, holy shit.
Hey, Sam. It's Nik.
I got your messages last night,
and I was super busy at work,
so there was no way
I was going out after.
So yeah, I guess I'll just
see you when I see you.
All right. Bye.
It's freezing in here.
You think?
I was gonna turn the air on.
You feel okay?
What are you doing home?
Well, I was on my break,
and I thought I would
pick some stuff up and...
You hear from the committee?
Can't make them get
back to me faster.
I don't know.
For 100 grand?
That could use some
follow-up, I think.
Can I see them?
Mom.
Slept in pretty late this morning.
Day's getting away from you.
I was out kind of late.
I heard.
So did the whole apartment
building when you came home.
Great.
Well, I'm gonna go get
ready to see Nikki.
Oh, what are you two gonna do?
You know, girly things.
I didn't think you were coming.
I said I would.
Are you going somewhere cold?
No, I-I think I'm
just getting sick.
Or hungover.
So how was work after I left?
Did you get my message?
Yeah.
How was your lover's?
Stop it.
I hate when you say that.
It was... okay.
Did you do anything fun?
No.
I missed you, though.
The flowers are looking good.
I actually got the Dendrobium
spectabile to bloom.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I have a
real shot at getting in.
Listen, if I get accepted,
could we talk about me moving?
Excuse me, but...
do I know you from somewhere?
I'm sorry?
I've seen you around before.
What's your name?
Oh, that's smooth.
I'm sorry?
She's not interested, mate.
Sorry to tell you that.
Put it this way:
you're not working with the
right equipment down there.
Are you done yet?
Yeah.
Fucking men.
Dinner is served.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna go sit down and eat?
Tonight we're having dinner
sitting at the table.
I'm not 12.
My roof, my rules.
Sit.
You know, I'm not gonna
be here much longer.
Then while you're here,
we're going to act like a family.
I can go get a hotel.
Why would you do that?
So I don't have to put up
with these ridiculous rules.
You and your roommate never
sat at the dinner table
and had dinner together?
My roommate?
Humor me.
No.
We didn't.
As you can imagine, we're
not your ordinary couple.
That's what this is about.
It's a part of not being ordinary.
Watch that.
I've been here ten days, and
you're already driving me nuts.
So where are you gonna go?
A hotel?
That'll last you a couple of weeks.
That's all I need.
That's what you said when you got here.
Your two weeks is coming up fast.
Everything's gonna work out.
We had a really good time today.
And what if it doesn't?
What's your plan?
Get my own place.
With what money?
With the money I get
from the flowers.
You haven't been following up.
How do you know
you're gonna get in?
You know what?
I don't want to talk about this.
Thanks for dinner.
Oh!
You okay?
Um... yeah.
It's... just cramps.
You sure?
I'm gonna lie down.
Do you need anything?
I'll be fine.
Fuck.
Shit! Oh!
Oh, shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
Are you making breakfast?
Oh!
What happened?
Oh, I burned my hand
on that damn coffeepot.
Are you cooking something?
No. Why?
No reason.
I'm fine, if you were wondering.
Shit.
Sorry.
Let me help you.
Thanks.
When are you going in?
I'm gonna leave here in a minute.
You can keep it.
I have more at work.
You slept in this morning.
You feeling okay?
Don't even start with that.
It's my job.
Not looking very well.
Thanks, Mom.
How are you feeling?
Fucking awful.
I've never had a hangover
that lasts more than a day.
That's good.
It means the alcohol is
cleansing you of your stress.
Hey, hold on.
Never mind. It can wait.
Ignoring her calls, huh?
Big one?
Shut up.
So did you get my text messages?
Fuck, I forgot to check them.
What's going on?
I've had the worst fucking morning.
I woke up to the fucking cops
at my house this morning.
What? Are you serious?
Yeah.
Well, what for?
They're looking for some guy
who was at my house
a couple nights ago.
No way. Who?
I don't know.
Some guy named Brent Jaffe.
Well, did they say why?
No, and they were being
really weird about it.
They wouldn't say much about it, just that
if I talked to anyone that knew anything
to give them a call.
So... do you know anything?
No, I don't.
That's crazy.
Hope it's nothing serious.
Well, it was serious enough
for the cops to
fucking wake me up.
No more randoms at my house.
I don't care how hot they are.
Did they show you a
picture or anything?
Yeah, but I didn't recognize him.
I was so fucked up that night.
Well, is anything missing
from your place?
Mo.
I'm, like, going through
everything right now, but...
I don't think so.
Well, listen, I got to go into work, but
I'll call you as soon as I'm out, okay?
Okay.
Bye, love.
Sam, you've got someone
in your section.
Okay. Thanks.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
Hey, Riley.
Hey.
Back again, huh?
Yup.
I know what I like.
Listen, about the other
night at Alice's.
I was not trying to...
No explanation needed.
And I'm sorry about
what Alice said.
Oh, no, don't be.
It was funny.
So you want the usual?
Yeah.
I...
Hey, can you switch
sections with me?
Yeah. Sure.
Hey.
How you guys doing?
Fine. How are you?
Good.
Oh, I'm fine, thanks.
What can I get you to drink?
I'll have a glass of
chardonnay, please.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
Glass of...
Chardonnay, please.
A-and for you, ma'am?
I'll have...
I'm gonna get you some water
and I'll be right back
with those drinks.
Hey, can you cover my table?
Where are you going?
I'll be just a minute.
Stop it!
Samantha?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'll be out in a second.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh!
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Just really bad cramps.
Do you need a tampon?
I'm gonna go take
care of this table.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Are you ready to order?
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
Ow.
Samantha?
Hello, Samantha.
How are you?
I'm okay.
Fine.
What seems to be the problem?
Well, I'm feeling kind of funny.
What kind of funny?
Well, this morning, I woke up,
and my stomach was killing me,
and then I went to the bathroom,
and there was blood...
there was a lot of blood.
Did you start your period?
I think so.
But something's wrong.
It's acting up.
Let's take a look.
Deep breath.
Again.
One more time.
Good.
Do you have a history
of heart problems?
Or anybody in your family?
No. Why?
Your heart rate
is unusually slow.
Hmm.
Hold still for me.
Hold still.
Okay, open wide for me.
Say, "Ah."
Ah.
Thank you.
So what is it?
Well, your ear canals appear
to be getting infected.
That could be a head
cold getting worse.
Now, the illness may be
lowering your immune system,
which may be lowering
your heart rate.
But that would not explain
the vaginal bleeding.
Shall we take a look?
W-w...
What if I told you there
was something else?
I-I have a rash... down there.
Lie back for me.
Samantha.
Samantha, are you sexually active?
Why?
I think you know why.
I'm a lesbian.
Have you ever been sexually
active with a man?
I will take that as a yes.
It-it was one time, last night...
two nights ago.
Samantha, if you're not
being truthful with me, I...
I swear.
It was the other night.
That's it.
I haven't been with a guy
in eight months until then.
Are you using protection?
I don't-I don't remember
if we did the other night.
Well, you definitely
have a severe rash.
Lot of dead skin, chafing.
Is there any discomfort?
God, yes.
You should apply some
moisturizing lotion
when you get home tonight.
What about the bleeding?
Unless it's some sort of
internal bleeding or...
an unknown pregnancy...
I told you, I...
The other night, that's it.
As far as I can tell you have
a head cold and 'a rash.
Sam.
I totally forgot
you were visiting.
Can I come in?
Aren't you supposed to be at work?
You know George is gonna be
pissed at you for missing again.
It was dead.
He cut me early.
Oh.
Good of you to stop by, then.
Yeah.
So how was work last night?
Oh, it was fucking awful.
There was this guy there that
was hitting on me all night.
Actually, he reminded
me of that fellow
that always comes in to see you.
Riley.
Yeah, that's him.
I just don't understand it.
It's like they know
they can't have us,
so they try even harder.
Finally I just told him, I said,
"I'm not gonna touch your cock."
Then he ran up a $200 tab
trying to impress me.
It was pathetic.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm okay.
I don't mean to be a twat,
but you look like shit.
Yeah...
I think that hangover
is sticking with me.
Right.
Anyway, I've got your post.
Oh, anything from the committee?
I've been waiting to hear back.
I don't know.
So I got us something.
Did you?
Today's ten months.
Oh. Right.
I didn't know we were
exchanging gifts.
It's kind of an odd
anniversary, right?
Well, I...
I just figured with everything
that's been going on,
it'd be nice.
Yeah.
Right.
The place looks nice.
Happy to see you kept my stuff.
Stop it.
What?
I miss you.
I miss us.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I guess.
Then let it happen.
You know, this is...
It's all just a wee bit
too fast for me.
Well, if you don't let things happen,
nothing's gonna get resolved.
You know, it's good to have space.
Fine.
I'm gonna go meet
Alice for dinner.
Oh. Dinner.
Stop it.
She wants to fuck you, you know.
Oh, my gosh.
What?
Like you're surprised?
You knew about this?
Well, isn't it obvious?
When did this come?
Oh, that.
Is that important?
Hey.
Sorry I was late.
Is it slow?
Dude, what the hell?
What?
Your fucking eye.
My eye?
What about it?
Go to the fucking bathroom.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
Holy shit!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I just wanted to check on you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm a little jumpy.
What the hell is
wrong with your eye?
I think there's something
caught in it or...
or, like, an allergic reaction.
Well...
you need to get it
looked at, because...
it looks super gross, man.
Thanks.
I'm serious.
What the fuck have
you been smoking?
Nothing. I...
I just left Nikki's.
Oh, yeah?
You guys working it out?
Maybe.
Great.
Hey, have you heard
anything about that guy
from the other night?
Oh. Yeah.
They put out an alert about him
on the fucking news this morning
like they do with child molesters.
I mean, they said he
could be dangerous.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Crazy.
Ow.
Honey, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Stay back.
Oh, my God.
What is wrong?
Be honest with me.
Nothing.
I'm just sick.
Are you pregnant?
What's that word you
love to call me so much?
Dyke?
No, I'm not pregnant.
Just leave me alone.
Oh, yeah.
I got in.
I'm proud of you.
What the fuck?
Mom, did you use
all the hot water?
What are you talking about?
Did you use all the hot water?
I haven't showered yet.
Well, there's not any hot water.
Are you kidding me?
It's like a sauna in here.
Look.
See? Nothing.
Oh, my God!
What?
Samantha!
Look at your hand!
I will not stand for this
in this house again.
Never again.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the doctor.
Where are you really going?
Get off my back.
Honey, I ask because I care.
You've been sleeping in late.
You're "sick."
That's how it started the last time.
This isn't last time.
You don't know where the
fuck I'm going every night.
I'm not this horrible person that
you think I am in your head.
I didn't say you were!
You don't have to say it!
What was that?
What did you do?
Excuse me?
What are you doing to yourself?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Your hair.
What the...
What is this?
What did you do?
You think I did this?
Fuck!
Sammy, where are you going?
Come back!
You...
Hey. It's George.
Where are you?
Fuck.
I'm sorry, George.
I'm headed to the doctor and
then I have to be somewhere.
The doctor?
Why didn't you ask off?
This is an emergency.
What, are you dying?
Hello?
No, but it is an emergency,
George.
Listen, I heard about yesterday.
I only have you on right now.
I need you to come in just for a little bit
until I can get someone to replace you.
Is that cool?
Hello?
Yeah. Okay.
I'll be there in a minute.
Fuck!
Hey, Sam.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You can't wear those.
I really need you to cut me
some slack here, George.
I'm cutting you slack, but I can't have
you look like slack at work, get it?
Holy shit.
What happened?
It's pinkeye.
Oh, that looks like some
really bad pinkeye.
I know.
The doctor. Remember?
Yeah.
You should go.
I mean, you look not well.
Try to squint or something.
Sorry about the wait.
Is there anything
else I can get you?
I think we'll be okay.
Great.
I will go check on your food.
I got Joey coming in for you.
You can take care of your
face when he gets here.
Hey, Sam?
Hey, Sam! Wait up!
Sam!
Hey, Sam! Hey.
What do you want?
I was just coming in to see you.
I figured you'd be working.
I got to go.
Wait.
Are you okay?
I'm not feeling well, okay?
And you need to stop coming
to see me all the time.
Do you want me to take
you to the doctor?
That's not your job.
I am not your problem.
You're a really nice guy,
but I'm not into you.
Wait.
I saw you the other night.
With that guy.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, you do.
You know what I'm talking about.
Now the cops are looking for him.
Were you spying on me?
Stay away from me, or I'll tell
'em about how you're stalking me.
Hey, I'm in the
middle of something.
Holy shit, dude.
Where have you been?
I just got off work.
What's wrong?
So they caught the
guy from the party,
and now the police are asking me
for a list of names of
anyone that was there.
They're questioning anyone that's
come into contact with him.
Are you serious?
Why?
I don't know, but it has
to be something bad.
Holy shit.
I mean, he was going
by his nickname, B.J.,
which is why his name didn't
sound familiar to anyone.
Did you meet anyone named B.J.?
I, um...
What?
Samantha?
What is it?
I have to go.
Wait!
What do you mean,
you don't know anything?
We have to wait for the
results of your blood test.
These things take time.
I don't have time.
Whatever's happening to
me is getting worse.
When did this happen?
Yesterday, after I left.
It looks to be viral, but...
there's no buildup that
would suggest infection.
What does that mean?
You're sure this happened
after you had sex...
unprotected sex?
Yes.
I can't be sure until I
see the test results,
but this appears to be some sort
of sexually transmitted disease.
Is-is there anything
you can give me?
Antibiotics? Cream?
Anything?
Anything I would give you could
be had over the counter.
The real treatment will happen
once I can identify what this is.
So what do I do?
Do not come into
contact with anyone
until we can determine what
it is we're dealing with.
Hey.
Hi.
What's up?
I'm in kind of a bind.
I need something to help me out.
What kind of bind are you in?
You need some cash?
Can I just come inside?
Yeah.
Sure.
Alice is on her way too, so...
just in time.
What are you looking for?
Something that'll help me get
through the next 48 hours.
You sound like you're
in some deep shit.
Want to talk about it?
No? Okay.
No worries.
Here.
Now, just be careful
with this stuff, okay,
because it's been a while.
Whew.
Ah. That's Alice.
Hey.
No, yeah.
Just come to the front.
I'll let you in.
All right.
Sam?
What the fuck?
What are you doing to her?
What?
She came here.
I've had a pretty fucked-up
last couple of days.
What's going on?
You know that guy,
B.J.?
Yeah.
Well...
I don't know what happened.
I was at your party,
and then we were in his car
and then I woke up at home.
It's all a blur.
Samantha, you have
to tell the police.
No, I can't!
You have to tell the
police what happened!
That's not it.
Something's been wrong with
me ever since that night.
Oh, I'm way too high for that.
Sam,
we need to take you to the police
so that you can tell
them what happened.
No, I can't go to the police.
I can't let Nikki find out.
Forget Nikki.
We have to think about you.
You would like that,
wouldn't you?
Me to forget Nikki.
What are you talking about?
Oh, don't act like you
haven't been waiting for us
to break up since the
moment you met her.
Okay.
Now I know you're high.
Fuck you!
Sam!
No, you don't care about
what's best for me.
You care about what's best for you.
If you fucking cared,
you'd help me hide this shit
and not try to expose it
so I can be left
with nobody but you!
Samantha!
Before you say anything,
I may have sold roofies to a guy
named B.J. at that party.
So...
Thanks, Joey.
Is George here?
Not right now.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't stay here too long.
He's pretty pissed
about the other day.
Doing okay?
Do you want to get out of here?
Let's go.
Listen, I want you to convince her
that what I'm doing is
right because it is right.
All right.
It is.
Sammy?
What are you doing home?
I'm going to sign in
for the weekend.
What's going on?
Dr. Sullivan and I wanted
to have a talk with you.
Why?
Have you been drinking?
What's this about?
Samantha, we just want you
to get the help you deserve.
I-I don't need any help.
Samantha, we could
go away together,
just you and me,
have a little time
just for one another.
You don't even know
what's wrong with me.
Then take off your glasses.
You think I'm on drugs.
I know you're on drugs.
I know you are back on drugs!
No, no, no!
I'm going to Nikki's.
No, no!
Nikki is enabling you.
That's right.
No!
Nikki is absolutely wrong for you.
We can get you through this...
together.
We've done it before.
We can do it again.
I don't even know who he is.
Y-you do not know what's
going on with me.
I'm really sorry that you don't approve of
your fucked-up daughter, but you know what?
You're not so perfect yourself.
You're looking for love from any men
that'll give you the time of day.
Are you gonna stay
sober this time?
Are you crazy?
You shut your mouth!
No, you listen to me!
Well, then talk, Samantha.
Tell us what's wrong.
You want to know what's wrong?
Fine!
Here!
I'm sorry.
Hi.
I'm here to sign in.
Okay, and do you have your ID?
Ah, yes, you have the
Dendrobium spectabile.
We're very excited to see it.
Well, this is it.
Can I see you without the glasses?
Just a second, please.
I'm so sorry, but we're
not gonna be able
to admit you into the competition.
What? Why not?
I-I've already gotten the letter.
I can go get it right now.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but there's nothing I can do.
Nikki, open up, please.
Nikki!
Nikki, I can hear your phone!
Please open up!
What's wrong?
I just want to talk.
Fuck off.
Nikki, what's wrong?
Alice told me all of it.
She what?
Yeah, about how you fucked
a man at her party.
About how you got loaded earlier.
Nikki...
Samantha, you fucked a man.
Wake up.
You're a confused little girl
going through a phase.
Nikki, I care about you.
Please don't do this to me.
Samantha, isn't it obvious?
I'm not into you anymore.
You've run your course.
Is there someone else?
Of course there's someone else.
There's always someone else, love.
Go away, Samantha.
I... fucking love you!
Alice!
What the fuck are you doing?
Why did you do it?
Why did you tell Nikki?
Because you're out of control!
You can't fucking stand us together!
You need some fucking
help, Samantha,
and you look like shit.
Fuck you, Alice!
Admit it!
I'm not saying shit to you.
Is this what you want?
You want me, right?
Well, here I am.
I'm all yours now.
Get out of my house.
No.
I mean it.
Get out of my house now!
Now!
You don't even know
what you made me do!
What did you do?
I'm all alone now.
Sam, I love you.
What I did is for your own good.
You fucked everything up.
Look at me.
This is what you wanted.
What the fuck?
Help me!
Don't come near me!
No, Alice.
Don't!
Alice, please, Alice!
I'm calling the police!
No, no, don't!
Get off of me, you freak!
I can't let you do this, Alice!
Help!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
No.
No. I'm so sorry, Alice.
But I can't let you do this!
Hello?
Hey, Riley.
It's Samantha.
Samantha, hey.
Is everything okay?
No.
I need someone to talk to.
Are you around?
Y-yeah, yeah, of course.
Where are you?
I'm at Alice's.
Hello?
Samantha?
I'm here.
Everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Where's Alice?
She's in the back.
So what's going on?
I just...
I needed someone to talk to.
Listen, I'm...
I'm really sorry about earlier.
It's not my place...
You don't need to be sorry.
You were just...
looking out for me.
Yeah.
I really do like you.
That's why I asked
you to come over.
I need someone.
Uh...
W-what about Nikki?
Or Alice?
No cares the way you do.
Um...
I'm a little confused.
I, uh...
I'm confused.
I-I thought you weren't into me.
I'm going through...
changes.
I need someone that cares.
I care.
I know you do.
You wouldn't... hurt me.
Would you?
No.
No, I never would.
Ever.
Take this off.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Shit!
Shit, shit!
What?
Um...
I don't have a condom.
You're fine.
Really?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Oh, God.
Does that feel okay?
Yeah, uh-huh.
That's okay.
Okay.
It kind of tingles.
It's tingling.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
Okay.
Oh, wait. Wait.
Oh, my God, you're really wet.
Aah! Aah!
What is that?
Wait. Wait. Wait.
There's something moving.
There's something moving in there.
Oh, my-oh, my God.
What the hell?
Oh, my God!
Riley!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh!
Don't come near me!
I swear to God!
Holy shit.
Mom?
Samantha, where are you?
I'm down the street from Alice's.
Are you in your car?
I just want to come home.
I'm gonna get you help, okay?
But you need to let me help you.
I want you to pull over.
You don't need to be driving.
You were right.
We'll get through this!
There's something wrong with me.
Here!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Whoa, ma'am, you need to sit down!
You've just been in accident!
Whoa! Hey, get back!
Ma'am, do you know
where you're at?
Sam?
Honey, it's me!
It's Mom!
Ma'am, stay where you are!
Ma'am, we need you
to stay where you are!
Don't do it!
I said stay right there!
Officer, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
She's my daughter!
She's my daughter.
Sam! Honey, it's me!
Come to me!
You can relax!
I'm here to help you!
It's gonna be okay!
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Steady ♪
♪ Patronize me ♪
♪ Patronize ♪
♪ The man you dreamed of ♪
♪ For days ♪
♪ Hold ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ In your ♪
♪ Hands ♪
♪ They're dirty ♪
♪ In your h-hands ♪
♪ So I can feel you ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Want to be alone ♪
♪ With me one more night ♪
♪ 'Cause ♪
♪ April ♪
♪ Comes ♪
♪ And April goes ♪
♪ Everybody knows ♪
♪ I am younger now ♪
♪ Old ♪
♪ Men ♪
♪ Try to go away ♪
♪ The sun is your face ♪
♪ And no one is coming home ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Oh, me, oh, me, oh, my ♪
♪ I will never die ♪
♪ As long as I have you ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪